<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ramona e.j. spence</title>
    <link>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ramona e.j. spence</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2022 Ramona Spence</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the Developer</title>
      <link>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Ramona, but you&amp;rsquo;ve seen my name on this page enough already.
I&amp;rsquo;m a pastry cook and baker striving to make a career change in to the software industry. A lot of my time is spent working on coding projects, contributing to open source software, and learning programming concepts via python.
Outside of work and career, I love to ride my bike, watch star wars and anime, and spend time with my cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding Bootcamp</title>
      <link>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/ccs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/ccs/</guid>
      <description>My adventure in software and programming began at a 12-week coding &amp;ldquo;bootcamp&amp;rdquo; immersive course at Carolina Code School. The course was intense and definitely immersive, as I did nothing else but code, sleep, eat, and code.
In that course, we started with some basics in HTML5, CSS and Javascript. Most of our time in that first two weeks was spent with CSS and then we moved on to learn principles of Object-Oriented programming in Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events API</title>
      <link>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/projects/events-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/projects/events-api/</guid>
      <description>Finding tech-related meetups that are in your area can be a bit of a pain when they&amp;rsquo;re often split among platforms. Code for Greenville aims to solve that problem for the Upstate of South Carolina by bringing these events to one place</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef&#39;s Notebook</title>
      <link>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/projects/chefs-notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonaspence.github.io/portfolio/projects/chefs-notebook/</guid>
      <description>As a pastry cook, I was responsible for creating desserts to run as specials. I kept the recipes for those creations in a little pocket-sized notebook. I wanted to create an app that could be used just the same way I used that notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
